(Sheldon:)overnight guest
notification clause.
(Leonard:)Okay, fine,
I-I'm a horrible human being.
(Leonard:)I'm the Darth Vader of Pasadena.
(Sheldon:)You're far too short
to be Darth Vader.
(Sheldon:)At best you might be
a turncoat Ewok.
My point is: Priya's gone
and it would be much better
if no one else found out
about us.
(Sheldon:)You mean you want me
to keep a secret?
(Howard:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)You know I can't
keep a secret.
(Leonard:)You can if you try.
(Leonard:)Think about
it this way:
um, if I were Batman
and you were Alfred,
(Leonard:)you'd keep that
secret, right?
(Sheldon:)Why do you get
to be Batman?
Because Batman has the secret.
(Sheldon:)Alfred has secrets, too.
(Leonard:)Like what?
Alfred knows
(Sheldon:)that Barbara Gordon
is Batgirl.
(Sheldon:)Which I've now just
told to Batman.
See, I cannot
keep a secret.
Ta-dah!
(Sheldon:)What?
Ta-dah.
(Sheldon:)It's short for...
♪ Da-da-da-da! ♪
(Leonard:)Kind of busy here, Sheldon.